' Services included in this file will be checked during scans and
' listed in the resulting security report. The status of each service
' (stopped or started) will be listed in the Results Details page in
' the report.  When editing this list, include the service name for
' each service you wish to be scanned on a separate line.
' The service name can be found by looking at the Properties for
' the service in the Services Control Panel applet.
MSFTPSVC
TlntSvr
W3SVC
SMTPSVC